juzdeals.com 2017-08-30

# Privacy Policy For Juzdeals

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides guidelines and conditions regarding the personal information that Juzdeals.com collects, and the ways in which Juzdeals.com uses that personal information.

  **Personal information collection**  
Juzdeals.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

Any information about your use of this website  
Any information that you provide while registering with the website  
Any information about transactions carried out over this website  
Any information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services  
Any other information that you send to Juzdeals.com

 **Using personal information**  
Juzdeals.com may use your personal information to:  
Administer this website  
Personalize the website for you  
Enable your access to and use of the website services  
Send to you products / information that we deem relevant before / during / after the purchase  
Supply to you services that you purchase  
Send you marketing communications via Email, SMS and/or Direct Call

Where Juzdeals.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Juzdeals.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

 **Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are small packets of data that are stored in your browser when you visit our site. Data stored includes, but not limited to, user preferences, session and other information. We use these information to understand our users better, customize our services and promote effective and tailored ads. In short, cookies allow us to improve overall user experience.

On certain pages on the site, third parties may also place or recognize unique cookies in your browser. The use of these cookies is not governed by this policy but is subject to their own policies and we do not have control over that.

You can choose to refuse or remove cookies. However if you do this, some website services or features may not function properly.

 **Ads on Third Party vendors**  
We do promotions on other third party sites, including Google, hence our ads are shown on these sites. However, our ads are completely independent of the the sites' policy, content, etc.

 **Securing your data**  
Juzdeals.com will take all reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Juzdeals.com will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

 **Cross-border data transfers**  
Information that Juzdeals.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Juzdeals.com or its subsidiaries / partners / affiliates operate, to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will not be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

 **Unsubscribe**  
1] Please open our newsletter sent to your registered e-mail address/s.  
2] Scroll to the bottom of the daily newsletter and click on the unsubscribe link.  
3] You will be directed to a page to confirm your decision; please click select “Unsubscribe” again; although we’d love it if you choose the other option.  
4] If you have trouble finding the link on our e-mail / are unable to visit the external page, please call us or drop us a line and we’ll unsubscribe you from our communications manually.

 **Updating this statement**  
Juzdeals.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

 **Other websites**  
This website may contain links to other websites; Juzdeals.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

 **Contact Juzdeals.com**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Juzdeals.com’s treatment of your personal information, please [contact juzdeals](https://www.juzdeals.com//support/contact/)
